number two the following pair of
structures are and again we have these
options identical enantiomers derse and
constitutional isomers we want to
compare these structures in the same way
we have something in line notation and
then we have a Newman projection you can
go either way we could convert the line
notation to a Newan projection but I
think we're used to looking at molecules
in line notation so why don't we go
ahead and convert the Newan projection
to line notation what we want to do here
is clearly we are looking at a be
we have this methyl down and this methyl
up in the back that's these two right
here now what else do we have in order
to look at this Newman projection what
we're really doing is we're looking down
this Bond right here if we were to do
that what would we see well if we see
the bromine going up and to the left
that means that that must be on the dash
Bond here because the dash bond is going
to the left it's going past the screen